{"data":[{"question":"To see the statue of liberty and ________ pictures from the top of the empire state building are two reasons for visiting New York city.","a":"taking","b":"take","c":"taken","d":"to take","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To see- to take: we use parallel structure with infinitive phrases","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't see the ________ of sitting on the beach all day.","a":"attract","b":"attractive","c":"attractiveness","d":"attractively","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We need a noun to fill in the blank","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Factoring is the process of finding two or more expressions whose product is equal ________ the given expression.","a":"to","b":"as","c":"with","d":"by","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Something is equal to something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Bricks baked in a kiln are much harder ________ that are dried in the sun.","a":"those","b":"than do those","c":"than those","d":"ones","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the comparative form of short adjective (hard)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Since infection can cause ________ fever ________ pain, it is a good idea to check a patient's temperature.","a":"both \/ as well as","b":"both \/ as good as","c":"both \/ with","d":"both \/ and","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Both... and: used to emphasize that something is true not just of one person, thing, or situation but also of another.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Schizophrenia, a behavioral disorder typified by a fundamental break with reality, ________ by genetic predisposition, stress, drugs, or infections.","a":"may be triggered","b":"may triggered","c":"may trigger","d":"may be trigger","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/could\/ will, may...): can\/could\/ will\/may...+ be +PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They asked us, Henry and ________, whether we thought that the statistics had been presented fairly and accurately.","a":"I","b":"me","c":"mine","d":"my","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Me: object form of \"I\".","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They thought that he was guilty ________ racial discrimination.","a":"of","b":"with","c":"for","d":"about","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be guilty of.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"In purchasing a winter coat, it is very important ________ it on with heavy clothing underneath.","a":"for trying","b":"to try","c":"of trying","d":"try","answer":"2","explain":"\n- It's important to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"What happened in New York ________ a reaction from city workers, including firemen and policemen who had been laid off from their jobs.","a":"was","b":"were","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense.\u00a0\n- Subject (what) is singular- was.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}